We would like to divide the teams by drawing lots!
Yes!
Seriously, uh, it's pretty important to have a good group of people.
It's important, isn't it?
It's interesting, isn't it?
It affects our shared relationships.
Close the door!
So who do you want to be with?
I want someone who lives alone.
I see.
From a backer.
Ah...
Well, what about you, Isshi?
Well, I want Haruma, who looks the most powerful.
That's good.
Haruma, too?
No, Haruma looks different.
Don't be shy.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
I'm coming.
Wait!
I'm just plain scared.
It's not funny.It's usually pretty unfunny.
I might laugh.
Only the breath.
I'm laughing a little too hard.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Just to the right.
All at once.
One, two, three.
Here.
We were laughing so hard we couldn't see.
I'm out.
Okay.
One, two, three.
nao
wh
nao wh
We are
oooo
0 apt to have a body camp in
Wow!
I can't see it!I can't see it because I can't see it.
Heirayan calendar
Surprisingly, I only handled it.
It's so important that I'm already here at CP
layers
ed.
This is not a big, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide, wide.
Is it done?
Left foot, left foot.
Shift it with your body and come to the right.
Come back here.
Front, front.
Right, right.
Come on, to the right.
Hang it in front of you.
I can't do it! I can't do it!
I can't do it anymore. I can't do it anymore. I can't do it anymore.
Put it on the front.
Put it on. - Put it on.
Keep going.
Ready?
front
left
RightRight
Help me.
It's over.
Changed.
English Tenga available
voodoo
ering
I'm not sure if I'm the one who can do it, or if I'm the one who can do it.
Hey, 12...
Twelve.
Right, left, right.
Aren't they good? They're good.
Aren't they good?
They dance so well together.
Ready!
Left!
You're off to a good start.
The race is about to begin.
I think...
The red team is a little bit...
They seem to be our rivals.It's like we're rivals.
We're...
We're all men.
We're all men, so we're going for the power type.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
You can't beat us.
I'm not into that green anymore.
To be honest...
Um...
Don't tell me I'm cheating.
This is the game.
Yes, sir.
One, two, three, four.
Wow!
Yeah!
Oh, man!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here!
It's so much easier than the last relay race, and everyone seems to be having a great time.My mind is so much easier than the last Ekiden, and everyone seems to be having a great time.
But the Ekiden was also a lot of work, but it was a lot of fun.
But I won't do it again.
Camping already...
It's camp and yikes, it's great!
I don't know, I think if you saw the first episode of the first one, you'd know what I mean.
I think if you watch the first episode of the first one, you'll see that I made a mistake when I said, "What is this, the first project? I made a mistake when I said, "What's the first project?
I said, "Camping, right? I said, "Camping.
I never thought it would come true....
I'm going to put it in.
And then we break it up.
Wow!
What? It's getting cooler today.
Shall we go?
Yeah?
No, seriously.
No, I got a stupid change of clothes.
I'm good at this.
I'm just going in.
We're just going to play in the river.
Hey, you're soaking wet.
I have a towel in my bag.
I'm so silly.
I have a towel right there.
I already did it!I already did it!
I've done it!
There's nothing left to do but get it back.
Oh, really...
What about me?
What are you going to do?
Hmmm...
You've got to do it.
It's okay.
It's good.
Let's go.
Yay!
I'll come back.
Take a picture.
Don't die in this river.
Be careful
It's going against the current.
Be really careful.
Just in time.
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm going against the current, so I didn't make any progress at all
Also, my clothes are heavy.
Wait a minute.Wait a minute.
Aahhh!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Watch out!
Laughter
Yoona was next to Mr. Eechi, and he just walked in.
It's true! It's your fault!
And then again, she was next to him, but only he went in.
I really don't get it.
Are you okay?
I have sandals downstairs, okay?
Yeah, you want to come with me?
Oh, you really want to?
I'm sure.
Okay.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Good job, sir.
What are we gonna do if we don't have fun?
Yes, of course!
Yes!Yes!
Then I'm going to ingest it!
Ready?
I'm in.
Watch out!
I'm scared!
We have to go this far. Isn't this fun?
Yeah, I guess so.
The ending.
This is a little worse.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Wow!
Scary.
Ouch.
Oh, no, you're not.
Two birds with one stone
You're the worst
Yes, sir.
Let's go downstairs.
We've already done it twice.
Let's go downstairs a second time.
What? Wait, why?
Why are we just doing this?
I don't know, it's just... I don't know, it's just for the camera.Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Let's get a shot and then we'll go.
Oh, wow.
I'm definitely going in.
I'm definitely not going in.
Wow.
You did it.
Please, please, please.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you fucking run away!
Hey, don't run!
Whoa! Oh, my God, it's so bad!
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, God, I'm done!
I'm done, I'm done!
I'm done!
Yeah!
Pang!
Ouch.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
There's a point in doing it like that, isn't there?
I can't do it anymore.I'm screwed.
Let's all go in the river together.
Let's get in the river.
Wow.
Cherish, cherish, cherish.
Thank the earth!
I'm making yakisoba!
Yay!
Wait, I've never made yakisoba before.
Really?
It's a lady.
It's really...
Let's cook!
Cooking!
We should have a cooking competition, right?
I'd love to!
Let's throw it in!
I want to have a showdown without looking at the recipe!
Very possible!
That's what Tsukanesan is supposed to do!
That's so cool!That's awesome cool!
Then this is a good frying pan, so it's slippery.
In a row, in a row, in a row.
Yes!
You did it!
I'm sorry.
I'll spit it out.
Can I taste it?
It doesn't taste like anything yet.
It's raw.
Help me.
Still?
A little water, a little water.
There's ants back there.
She's useless.
You're a useless woman.
If you did it like this, I'd do it like this.
Oh, no!
You're good!
Thank you very much.
I've never made yakisoba before.
First time in your life, Mr. Unruh.
No, I cook eggs.
It's like you can't cook.
We've already had Toba.We've already done that.
Mr. Unley, it's in slow motion.
No way. I'm really not happy.
Let's fry it up and try it like this.
What? What? What?
Oh, my God, that's Ursides!
Boober, no more!
I'm good at bug-roasting, aren't I?
I'm good at frying bugs, aren't I?
Can I say something for real?
Yes, please.
I never thought I'd get to eat with Rina Iizuka and Yuna Yajima.
It's really true! At first...
The members have been telling me this for a long time, and it's scary, scary, scary.
I was already scared of Iizuka-san and Yajima-san.
They don't say anything, they don't talk, they don't change...
Listen to me!
It was the first time I met them.
I was so overwhelmed by how well they dance.
I couldn't speak well.
I couldn't speak properly, so I had to use long-winded keigo in my first conversation on the line.
I was so overwhelmed by their dancing skills that I couldn't speak properly. It was like, "Can I talk to you?
He seemed to notice.
I'm sorry, I was just trying to communicate.
I'm pretty impressed because I didn't think I'd be able to have dinner with someone who said, "I'm sorry, I'm just trying to communicate with you.I'm pretty impressed because I didn't think I'd be able to have dinner on such good terms with someone who said, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We didn't exchange lines for about 6 months after we first met.
I didn't know that.
Yuna and Miyu said they wouldn't exchange lines with anyone together.
I gave it to everyone and we exchanged.
They were all young dancers, you know?
I remember exchanging lines with Eechi.
I remember exchanging lines with Ici.
Seriously?
That was the first time I went down to the bottom.
Yeah, and then we'd get down on our knees like this.
That bad?
He said, "Please exchange lines with me.
I don't get it.
He didn't say that much.
That's what I want.
The members, or rather, all the boys called all the girls by their last names except for Ici.
For example, Yajima-san.
Nowadays, they call us by our first names.
Andy, Reno, Miyu, Ici, Yajima.
What? You can say it now. I've never been called that before. Never.
Say it once.
He hasn't said it. He hasn't said it. I'm sure it's never been said.
I call everyone by their last names except for Ichi.
I have a father in Mt. Sasaki too.Mt. Sasaki has a father, too.
But I remember that Amu suddenly called me "Yuga" when we danced as a pair in August.
It was too rare.
You're shaking.
Oh, no.
I'm Shunki.
That's right.
What's your best impression?
Am I right?
I don't know what to think of you.
It wasn't even close.
It really wasn't.
Well, can I tell you what I remember most about you?
The first thing,
When we went into that studio.
We met at the Voight, all 10 of us.
Mixed gender.
And I was so nervous.
I got dizzy.
And I think that's where I got, you know...
I got, you know, sick.
I see... so you can eat with everyone now.
It's true.
Thank you so much.Thank you for being such a good friend to me.
for letting me be friends with you.
I'm going to challenge you to a game of
Earphone Gun Gun Game!
Yeah!
It's an earphone gun game!
Smoke, smoke
Smoke.
Smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke.
Junior... Junior... Junior 2...
Two in the middle.
Two... two... two... two... two... two...
Two. - Two.
Second grade.
Tokyo!
I'm lost!
Wait! Tokyo Dome!
I know where it is! Idiot!